<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Skin Helper</string>
    <string name="CancerChecker">tflitetest</string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">AIzaSyDWQqO77ockRrGXVeeGL6LhUNUsBwapPOA</string>

    <string name="Actinic_keratosis">Actinic keratosis</string>
    <string name="Actinic_keratosis_description">An actinic keratosis (ak-TIN-ik ker-uh-TOE-sis) is a rough, scaly patch on the skin that develops from years of sun exposure. It\\\'s often found on the face, lips, ears, forearms, scalp, neck or back of the hands.\n\nAlso known as a solar keratosis, an actinic keratosis grows slowly and usually first appears in people over 40. You can reduce your risk of this skin condition by minimizing your sun exposure and protecting your skin from ultraviolet (UV) rays. Left untreated, the risk of actinic keratoses turning into a type of skin cancer called squamous cell carcinoma is about 5% to 10%.</string>
    <string name="Actinic_keratosis_link">https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/actinic-keratosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20354969</string>

    <string name="Basal_Cell_Carcinoma">Basal Cell Carcinoma</string>
    <string name="Basal_Cell_Carcinoma_description">Basal cell carcinoma is a type of skin cancer. Basal cell carcinoma begins in the basal cells — a type of cell within the skin that produces new skin cells as old ones die off. Basal cell carcinoma often appears as a slightly transparent bump on the skin, though it can take other forms. Basal cell carcinoma occurs most often on areas of the skin that are exposed to the sun, such as your head and neck.\n\nMost basal cell carcinomas are thought to be caused by long-term exposure to ultraviolet (UV) radiation from sunlight. Avoiding the sun and using sunscreen may help protect against basal cell carcinoma.</string>
    <string name="Basal_Cell_Carcinoma_link">https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/basal-cell-carcinoma/symptoms-causes/syc-20354187</string>

    <string name="Seborrheic_Keratosis">Seborrheic Keratosis</string>
    <string name="Seborrheic_Keratosis_description">Seborrheic keratosis (seb-o-REE-ik ker-uh-TOE-sis) is a common benign skin growth, similar to a mole. Most people will have at least one in their lifetime. They tend to appear in mid-adulthood and their frequency increases with age. They are harmless and don’t require treatment, but you can have them removed if they bother you.\n\nSkin growths like seborrheic keratoses are sometimes also called epidermal tumors. That doesn’t mean they’re cancer, though. Technically, moles and warts are also epidermal tumors. That just means they are clusters of extra cells on the epiderma, the outer layer of the skin. They aren’t considered a risk factor for skin cancer.</string>
    <string name="Seborrheic_Keratosis_link">https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21721-seborrheic-keratosis</string>

    <string name="Dermatofibroma">Dermatofibroma</string>
    <string name="Dermatofibroma_description">Dermatofibroma, also known as fibrous histiocytoma, is a common, benign, cutaneous soft-tissue lesion characterized by firm subcutaneous nodules. The term "fibrous histiocytoma" primarily describes the morphologic appearance of the cell populations forming these lesions rather than solely indicating the cellular lineage. Clinically, these mesenchymal cell lesions of the dermis are commonly found on the extremities and are relatively small, typically measuring 1 cm or less in diameter. Dermatofibromas are prevalent across all age groups; however, they are more frequently observed in individuals aged 20 to 50, especially among females.\n\nDermatofibromas are typically asymptomatic but may sometimes cause pain, tenderness, or itchiness. The lesions represent a benign dermal proliferation of fibroblasts. Despite the unknown pathogenesis, sometimes dermatofibroma may occur due to insect bites, trauma, minor injuries, or superficial puncture wounds. Although dermatofibromas are benign tumors, cases of local recurrence and, even more rarely, distant metastases have been reported. Therefore, when considering the differential diagnosis of these lesions, it is crucial to distinguish dermatofibroma from dermatofibrosarcoma protuberans (DFSP)—a similar-appearing but more aggressive cutaneous neoplasm.</string>
    <string name="Dermatofibroma_link">https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK470538/#:~:text=Dermatofibroma%2C%20also%20known%20as%20fibrous,prevalent%20across%20all%20age%20groups</string>

    <string name="Melanoma">Melanoma</string>
    <string name="Melanoma_description">Melanoma is a kind of skin cancer that starts in the melanocytes. Melanocytes are cells that make the pigment that gives skin its color. The pigment is called melanin. Melanoma typically starts on skin that\\\'s often exposed to the sun. This includes the skin on the arms, back, face and legs. Melanoma also can form in the eyes. Rarely, it can happen inside the body, such as in the nose or throat. The exact cause of all melanomas isn\\\'t clear. Most melanomas are caused by exposure to ultraviolet light. Ultraviolet light, also called UV light, comes from sunlight or tanning lamps and beds. Limiting exposure to UV light can help reduce the risk of melanoma.\n\nThe risk of melanoma seems to be increasing in people under 40, especially women. Knowing the symptoms of skin cancer can help ensure that cancerous changes are detected and treated before the cancer has spread. Melanoma can be treated successfully if it is found early.</string>
    <string name="Melanoma_link">https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/melanoma/symptoms-causes/syc-20374884#:~:text=deeper%20skin%20layers.-,Melanoma%20is%20a%20kind%20of%20skin%20cancer%20that%20starts%20in,%2C%20back%2C%20face%20and%20legs</string>

    <string name="Melanocytic_Nevi">Melanocytic Nevi</string>
    <string name="Melanocytic_Nevi_description">Melanocytic nevi are benign tumors that arise in the skin. They have different sizes and colors as outlined above. Benign nevi are usually round or oval-shaped and are uniform in color. There are more nevi in areas of the body that have greater long-term exposure to the sun, such as the outer arm compared with the inner arm.\n\nCells within the skin called melanocytes produce a pigment named melanin. This pigment is what gives melanocytic nevi a tan to dark brown color. Melanin is also responsible for overall skin color and the darkening seen with a sun tan.</string>
    <string name="Melanocytic_Nevi_link">https://www.yalemedicine.org/conditions/melanocytic-nevi-moles#:~:text=Overview,a%20melanoma%EF%BB%BF%20within%20them</string>

    <string name="Vascular_lesions">Vascular lesions</string>
    <string name="Vascular_lesions_description">Vascular lesions are relatively common abnormalities of the skin and underlying tissues, more commonly known as birthmarks. There are three major categories of vascular lesions: Hemangiomas, Vascular Malformations, and Pyogenic Granulomas. While these birthmarks can look similar at times, they each vary in terms of origin and necessary treatment.\n\nAt SSM Health Cardinal Glennon Children’s hospital, the SLUCare Physician Group pediatric plastic surgery team is committed to creating an individualized care plan for vascular lesions that improves the physical and emotional well-being of your child.</string>
    <string name="Vascular_lesions_link">https://www.ssmhealth.com/cardinal-glennon/services/pediatric-plastic-reconstructive-surgery/hemangiomas</string>

    <string name="Intraepithelial_Carcinoma">Endometrial intraepithelial carcinoma</string>
    <string name="Intraepithelial_Carcinoma_description">Endometrial intraepithelial carcinoma (EIC) is a recently described lesion characterized by replacement of endometrial surface epithelium or glands by malignant cells resembling high-grade invasive endometrial carcinoma. EIC has been identified in a high proportion of uteri containing serous carcinoma, but its association with other endometrial tumors is unknown. To determine the strength and specificity of the association of EIC with tumors displaying serous differentiation, the appearance of the endometrium in 38 uteri with serous carcinoma, 113 with endometrioid carcinoma, and 34 with malignant mixed mesodermal tumor (MMMT) were compared. EIC was present in 34 (98%) uteri with serous carcinoma compared with 7 (6%) uteri removed for endometrioid carcinoma (P = .0001). Hyperplasia without atypia was found in only 2 (5%) of 38 serous carcinomas compared with 38 (34%) of 113 endometrioid carcinomas.\n\nSimilarly, atypical hyperplasia was not found in any uterus with serous carcinoma, but was present in 14 (12%) uteri with endometrioid carcinoma (P = .02). The endometrium was inactive or atrophic in 29 (76%) patients with serous carcinoma compared with 33 (29%) with endometrioid carcinoma (P = .0001). EIC was found in five (56%) of nine MMMTs with a serous epithelial component (serous-MMMT) compared with one (4%) of 25 MMMTs with an endometrioid epithelial component (endometrioid-MMMT). As with endometrioid and serous carcinomas, hyperplasia with and without atypia was more common with endometrioid-MMMTs as compared with serous-MMMTs. Hyperplasia was found in 25 (100%) and atypical hyperplasia in 8 (32%) of 25 endometrioid-MMMTs, but in none of the nine serous-MMMTs. This study shows that EIC is frequently and specifically associated with uterine tumors displaying serous differentiation. The findings suggest that EIC represents a form of intraepithelial tumor growth characteristic of serous carcinoma and serous MMMT and that EIC is the likely precursor of these neoplasms. In addition, the findings provide further evidence supporting the view that MMMTs represent variants of carcinoma not sarcoma.</string>
    <string name="Intraepithelial_Carcinoma_link">https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/7590702/#:~:text=Endometrial%20intraepithelial%20carcinoma%20(EIC)%20is,high%2Dgrade%20invasive%20endometrial%20carcinoma</string>

</resources>